## **Profile**

An inventive person with 3.2 years of work experience 3.6 in Annotation and 2.3 years as Talent Acquisition Specialist and achieve short time promotion in both fields with 100% Quality and implementing successful innovative strategies, strong interpersonal communication skills.

### Contact



1/A Nadar Thottam,Ummar Nagra Podanur Coimbatore, Tamilnadu Pin : 641023



+https://wa.me/+919500401907



asheer1617@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/m ohamm ed-zamasheer-45436522b/

#### **MOHAMMED ZAMASHEER A M**

Bachelor degree graduate (BCOMCA)

### REVIEWER

## **Career Objective**

To gain employment in a reputed organization or institution that offers me a consistently positive atmosphere to learn new technologies and implement them for the betterment of my entire career. Providing opportunities to show my skill and abilities to the work to get it appreciated.

## **Experience**

June 2022- Present

Mercedes Benz Research and development

#### Reviewer \ Team leader

- Working on data annotations process under Landmark Annotation/seat occupancy detection, Tyre Annotation
- Recognize facial landmarks such as eyes,eye iris, eyebrows, ears, nose, nasian, forehead, mouth, and jawline etc...
- Take a part of review/validation of annotated data.
   Adaptability for the quick learn and implementing the strategies to get the things better.
- Identified and resolved process issues to drive optimal workflow.
- primary responsibilities will include identifying and labeling named entities in text, classifying documents, validating machine learning model
- outputs, and identifying patterns in data
   Utilized annotation tools and platforms to label
   various types of data, such as images, videos, Lidar
   and segmentation according to project specifications.
   Conducted quality assurance checks on annotated
   data to identify and rectify errors, ensuring the
   reliability of labeled datasets and Maintained
   detailed documentation of annotation processes,
   ensuring clear communication and knowledge
   sharing within the team.
- Accurately annotated large datasets for ML, Ai projects, ensuring high-quality labeled data for model training
  - In this role, you will collaborate with our data science team and play a vital part in handling large textual data sets
- Providing training to the whole team regarding various work cultures and newly emerging eras in the project requirements.
- Performed Quality check on delivery.
- Evaluating them and giving corrective actions to gain maximum productivity with 100% quality.
- Assisted in the development of annotation guidelines and documentation to maintain data quality standards.
- Participated in regular training sessions to enhance annotation skills and stay updated with new tools and methodologies.

March 2021 - June 2022

Mobius 365
Data Services
Pvt.Ltd

### **Senior Process Associate**

- Talent Acquisition Sourcing Profiles from job portal
- Worked on different projects with a team managing power.
- Sending Emails to the suitable candidates as per requirement
- Reporting to Manager

## Software skills

Ira platform
kognic
conti
carrier builder
label box
naukri
Popular data annotation platforms
PPT Presentation
MS Office (All)
Ms Excel

## Languages

English Malayalam Tamil Hindi

## **Personal details**

 Age
 24

 Date of birth
 17/07/1999

 Gender
 Male

 Mother tongue
 Tamil

 Religion
 Muslim

 Blood group
 B+

## Reference

Office address

Mercedes Benz research and development Pin - 560037 Bangalore, India

## **Education**

2017 - 2020

VLB Janakiammal
College of Arts and
Science

#### BCOM (Bachelor of Computer Application)

- Bharathiar University
- Secured first class

2015 - 2017

Sri vishwaraya vidhyala higher secondary **Commerce - Computer Application** 

- State Board, Tamil Nadu
- 62% scored

2015

Vidhiya Vikas matriculation higher secondary School

#### **SSLC**

- Matriculation, Tamil Nadu
- 64% scored

# **Key roles held**

- Team Leadership and Management .
- Goal Setting and Performance Management .
- Quality Assurance and Process Improvement.
- Project Planning and Execution.
- Employee Development and Coaching.

## **Achievements**

- Secured the achievement as short time promotion as QA
- · Received the achievement for the Best Quality Performer Award
- Secured first class for B com CA graduation from Bharathiar University. Secured my team from getting lops
- Presented paper on the topic ONLINE MARKETING
- Has achieved 116 % productivity with 100% quality
- . STUDENT placement coordinator, VLBJCAS for the year 2018-2019